fisherbikes.com 2008-12-17

# Privacy Policy | Gary Fisher Mountain Bikes

This website, www.fisherbikes.com, is operated by Trek Bicycle Corporation, a Wisconsin corporation. We can be contacted by mail at 801 West Madison Street, Waterloo, Wisconsin 53594 USA and by email through our contact us page.

Trek is committed to respecting and protecting your privacy. We have established this privacy policy to demonstrate the care with which we will treat your information. This Policy is subject to change without notice.

**PRIVACY**

We will always respect your privacy and any personal information that you give us. We will always endeavor to comply with any data protection legislation currently in force.

**USE OF YOUR INFORMATION**

The following policy describes how we intend to use your personal information. If this differs for any reason, such as relating to children, we will make this clear at the time of data collection.

If you make a specific request for us to contact you, such as requesting a brochure, we will use the personal information you provide to fulfill your inquiry. At any page on this website where you have the opportunity to leave your personal information, you will be given the opportunity to object to us making further use of your data.

Otherwise, Trek may use the data given to contact you in the future for research purposes and/or marketing purposes, which may include information and offers about our range of products. The information may be passed to and processed by affiliated and subsidiary companies of Trek Bicycle Corporation and agents and other representatives who act under our direction. Some of Trek’s subsidiaries and affiliates are located outside the USA and any personal data that might be transferred to them or its other subsidiaries will be treated as set forth in this Policy, unless otherwise required by local regulations.

Trek will not pass your details to unrelated third party organizations.

**RIGHT TO OBJECT**

You have the right to request to have us correct any inaccuracies in the personal data we hold about you and change your mind about the usage rights you have given us. You may also object to your personal data being transferred out of the USA. You also have the right to ask us for a copy of the information about you which we hold on our systems. You can do any of these things by writing or emailing us at the above addresses. We reserve the right to take the necessary steps to verify your identity before acting on your request and may charge you a small fee to cover administrative costs.

**CHILDREN**

Trek may occasionally create on-line games and other attractions which children may play. Parents should supervise their children's online activities and consider using parental control tools available from online services and software manufacturers that help provide a kid-friendly online environment. These tools can also prevent children from disclosing online their name, address, and other personal information without parental permission.

**SECURITY**

Trek strictly protects the security of your financial information and your choices for its intended use. We use current industry standard technology to maintain the confidentiality and accuracy of any financial information you provide to us. We use “secure servers” with industry standard SSL 128 bit key encryption whenever financial information is transferred. However, we cannot guarantee that any information you submit to us will be free from unauthorized third party intrusion.

**COOKIES**

We use cookies to enhance the level of service we provide to you. These are sets of information automatically gathered by your computer whenever you enter some pages of the web site. They record the areas of the site you visit and the length of time you spend viewing them. You can set your computer to let you know when a cookie is issued or you can choose to disable them (although this may prevent you from viewing and otherwise using our website.)
